sommos

Curriculum vitae



vyara@sommos.work +34 652 751 804

VYARA

SUMMARY

She is very sharp in execution and planning events. An extremely client oriented freelance with high self confidence. Great effectivity in problem solving.

Her main areas of expertise are onsite coordination of big scale events and pre- and post-event planning.

EDUCATION

2011

B.A in Internacional Tourism Management in University of Applied Sciences Bremen, Germany

2006

C2 Cambridge Certificate of Proficiency in English

2009/2010

CETT Barcelona, Erasmus Program

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

June 2017 - Present

Freelance Event Manager

Overall project management, Guest management, Location management, Logistics, Production coordination.

Working on RFPs, planning of confirmed projects, budget control and final billing

Onsite management for events from 10 to 10.000 participants

Some projects:

The New MAN Truck Generation Launch Event, Bilbao 2020 I All-New SEAT Leon World Premiere, Barcelona 2020 I CLT Porsche Taycan, Mallorca 2019 I Oriflame Gold Conference, Mallorca 2019 I IDEA & CDEA Mercedes-Benz Trucks, Barcelona 2019 I Maersk Global Sales Conference, Madrid 2019 I Ooredoo Pavilion MWC, Barcelona 2019 I Audia Dealer Meeting, Marbella 2019 I SEAT Integrity Days, Barcelona 2018 I CLT Cupra, Barcelona 2018 I Volvo Ocean Race, Alicante 2017

January 2018 - May 2018

Corporate & events manager in We Barcelona, event agency

Managed a team of project managers Directed creation, definition and coordination of work processes and procedures. Supported the management board in the development of corporate strategy to secure accomplishment of the common company goals.

April 2014 - December 2016

Senior account manager in Eventisimo, Event production agency

Responsible for the full project cycle, from receiving and analyzing the briefings, through proposal stage, client presentation and pre-event organization to onsite coordination and post-event evaluation and billing process.

Office manager, training and supervision of more junior colleagues

+34 652 751 804

VYARA

Some projects:

Audi NIPS Conference Evening Event, Barcelona 2016 | Siemens SGT 800 User Group Meeting, Barcelona 2016 | SwitchMed Connect, Barcelona 2016 | CITROËN Retailer & Dealer Training, Barcelona 2016 | BMW M2 Product Launch Training, Barcelona 2016 | BMW M Track Days & M Sales Award, Barcelona 2016 | Bentley Bentayga Global Media Drive, Marbella 2015 | BASF Creator Space Tour, Barcelona 2015 | Lamborghini Global Dynamic Launch, Barcelona 2015 | BMW R 1200 R International Press Launch, Alicante 2014 | ŠKODA Fabia World Dealer Conference, Valencia 2014





REFERENCES

Would you like to work with Vyara?

